# Scott Gangemi

## Hey there,

I'm Scott. I'm a full stack developer and I'm passionate about building cool applications, and seeing the impact of awesome work.

My favourite thing about software development is creating fantastic experiences that people will love, and want to keep coming back to.





**Call me** 0431 987 232



or don't.
s.gangemi@me.com



scottgangemi.com github.com/Gangezilla

### Experience

### Domain Feb 2018 - Now Javascript Developer (Full Stack)

My key accomplishment has been to transition to Full Stack Developer, working across React and Node codebases.

 Building React components, and solving problems on several Node servers.

#### Domain Apr 2017 - Feb 2018 Front End Developer

The most important achievement my team and I worked towards was:

 Rebuilding Domain's listings pages and transitioning away from a legacy monolith code base.

#### APG & Co. 2016 - 2017 Junior Web Developer

Some of my teams best accomplishments were:

- Redesigned our bloated six page checkout into a sleek one page wonder.
- Tore out all of our old CSS and converted it to SASS (cutting off 300kb in the process).
- Rewrote thousands of lines of mystery JavaScript into easy to understand React.

# Volunteering

#### **NodeGirls**

I've mentored and taught at NodeGirls a number of times and have:

- Mentored individuals in an Express class.
- Helped to organise and run a React workshop.

### Education

#### **UTS**

2012 - 2015

Bachelor of Integrated Product Design: Major in Interaction Design

### Skills

I'm really comfortable with:

- HTML
- React
- CSS
- Express
- JavaScript
- Node

I'm currently working on:

- Python
- C#
- Learning computer science fundamentals
- Building stuff and learning new things.